wikisexguide.com 2017-06-06

# WikiSexGuide:Privacy policy - WikiSexGuide - International World Sex Guide

## Uses of Information

Your information is used to fulfill your requests and communicate with you, operate, support and improve our sites, products and services, conduct internal research, and personalize the content, products, services and advertisements offered to you. 

## Personal Information

We collect personal information for various business purposes when you interact with us, such as providing you with a subscription, processing your order, responding to requests for service or assistance, creating and improving our products and services, suggesting additional or different products or services, and protecting our rights and property. We collect information about you in two basic ways. First, we receive information directly from you. Second, through use of cookies and other technologies, we keep track of your interactions. 

## Information Sharing

We do not sell, rent or provide your personal information to third parties that are unaffiliated with Wikisexguide. Your personal information is shared with third parties with your consent, except in circumstances where the law requires it to be shared. 

## The Public and Collaborative Nature Of The Projects

All Projects of the Wikisexguide are collaboratively developed by its users using the MediaWiki software. Anyone with Internet access (and not otherwise restricted from doing so) may edit the publicly editable pages of these sites with logging in as a registered user. By doing this, editors create a published document, and a public record of every word added, subtracted, or changed. This is a public act, and editors are identified publicly as the author of such changes. All contributions made to a Project, and all publicly available information about those contributions, are irrevocably licensed and may be freely copied, quoted, reused and adapted by third parties with few restrictions. 

## 

WikiSexGuide does require editors to register with a project. Anyone can edit with logging in with a username. Users that do register are identified by their chosen username. Users select a password, which is confidential and used to verify the integrity of their account. Once created, user accounts will not be removed. It may be possible for a username to be changed, depending on the policies of individual projects. Wikisexguide does not guarantee that a username will be changed on request. 

## Purpose Of The Collection Of Private Information

Wikisexguide limits the collection of personally identifiable user data to purposes which serve the well-being of its projects, including but not limited to the following: 

To enhance the public accountability of the projects. Wikisexguide recognizes that any system that is open enough to allow the greatest possible participation of the general public will also be vulnerable to certain kinds of abuse and counterproductive behavior. Wikisexguide and the project communities have established a number of mechanisms to prevent or remedy abusive activities. For example, when investigating abuse on a project, including the suspected use of malicious “sockpuppets” (duplicate accounts), vandalism, harassment of other users, or disruptive behavior, the IP addresses of users (derived either from those logs or from records in the database) may be used to identify the source(s) of the abusive behavior. This information may be shared by users with administrative authority who are charged by their communities with protecting the projects. 

To provide site statistics. The Foundation statistically samples raw log data from users' visits. These logs are used to produce the site statistics pages; the raw log data is not made public. 

To solve technical problems. Log data may be examined by developers in the course of solving technical problems and in tracking down badly-behaved web spiders that overwhelm the site. 

## Disclaimer

Wikisexguide believes that maintaining and preserving the privacy of user data is an important value. This Privacy Policy, together with other policies, resolutions, and actions by wikisexguide, represents a committed effort to safeguard the security of the limited user information that is collected and retained on our servers. Nevertheless, Wikisexguide cannot guarantee that user information will remain private. We acknowledge that, in spite of our committed effort to protect private user information, determined individuals may still develop data-mining and other methods to uncover such information and disclose it. For this reason, Wikisexguide can make no guarantee against unauthorized access to information provided in the course of participating Wikisexguide Projects or related communities. 

## Controller of Personal Data and Data Storage

WikiWebGuides B.V. is the controller of your personal data collected under this Privacy Policy. Should you have any questions regarding Wikisexguide's privacy practices, you may contact us at: info@wikisexguide.com 

All personal data collected in this Privacy Policy is stored within the European Economic Area. 

## See Also

  * Wikisexguide:General disclaimer
  * Wikisexguide:Copyrights

Username* (Remember this for your future logins)

Password*

#### If you don't have an account

**Create account now!**

Confirm password*

Email* (Confirmation link will be sent to this email)

EMAIL CONFIRMATION REQUIRED TO DO ANY EDITS 

Already have an account? **Login Now**
